Guide to the Syria Collection of photographs AD.MC.036
Akkasah: Photography Archive (NYU Abu Dhabi)
- Studio Portraits (Box 2, Box 3, Box 4)
  - A studio portrait of a man wearing a suit., Circa 1955-1975; ref556; Studio Najah, Damascus (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 10.3 x 7.2 cm (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Men; Facial Hair; Facial Hair; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a boy., 19 November 1969; ref557; Photo Al Andalous, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 x 7.4 cm (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - A studio portrait of a boy., 1972; ref558; Above Cinema Mounir, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.2 x 7.2 cm (Box 4, Folder 2)
    Boys; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints; Children
  - A studio portrait of a boy., March 1970; ref559; Studio Al Khayyam, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 11.5 x 8.1 cm (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - A studio portrait of a young man., Circa 1955-1975; ref560; Studio Al-Rabih, (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 10.2 x 7.1 cm (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Men; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a boy., 1971; ref561; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 9.8 x 7.5 cm (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Boys; Children; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing; Syria
  - A studio portrait of a man with a mustache., 15 July 1987; ref562; Qusai, Aleppo, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 9.8 x 6.7 cm (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Aleppo, Syria; Men; Facial Hair; Facial Hair; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A studio portrait of a man with a mustache., 1984; ref563; Qusai, Aleppo, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 9.6 x 6.8 cm (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Men; Facial Hair; Facial Hair; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Arabic Writing; Syria
  - A studio portrait of a boy wearing a turtleneck., Circa 1955-1975; ref564; Studio Al-Rabih, (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 10.2 x 7.1 cm (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - A studio portrait of one man in two outfits, a suit and a military uniform., Circa 1955-1975; ref565; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 x 7.4 cm (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Gelatin Silver Prints; Uniforms; Military/Soldiers; Facial Hair; Syria; Men
  - A studio portrait of one man in two outfits, a turtleneck and a military uniform., Circa 1955-1975; ref566; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 x 7.4 cm (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Men; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria
  - A group portrait of two men in uniform smiling., Circa 1955-1975; ref567; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.3 x 6 cm (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Men; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Uniforms; Military/Soldiers; Syria; Arabic Writing; Group Portraits; Medals/Insignia
  - A group portrait with a man in uniform, a woman wearing glasses, and four little girls wearing bows., 17 August 1981; ref568; Photo Monsour, Damascus (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 8.5 x 6.5 cm (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Damascus, Syria; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Girls; Children; Men; Women; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Uniforms; Military/Soldiers; Jewelry; Facial Hair
  - A studio portrait of a young man wearing a suit., 12 February 1973; ref569; Studio Minas (Chouhada, Salhiyeh, Damascus, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 10 x 7.1 cm (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Men; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria
  - A studio portrait of a man with a mustache., 1980; ref570; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 x 7.4 cm (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Men; Facial Hair; Facial Hair; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Studio Photography; Individual Portraits
  - A studio portrait of a boy., Circa 1955-1975; ref571; Studio Al-Rabih, (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 x 7.4 cm (Box 4, Folder 3)
    Boys; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria; Children
- Vernacular Series (Box 4)
  - A group portrait of six young men sitting outdoors., 24 October 1970; ref572; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.3 x 7.2 cm (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Men; Damascus, Syria; Outdoors; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A group portrait of a woman and two smiling children outside (linked ref 574)., Circa 1965-1975; ref573; Apamis, Aleppo, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.3 x 7.2 cm (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Aleppo, Syria; Women; Children; Girls; Boys; Outdoors; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints
  - A group portrait of a woman and a man in military uniform outside (linked ref 573)., Circa 1965-1975; ref574; Apamis, Aleppo, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.2 x 7.2 cm (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Aleppo, Syria; Men; Women; Uniforms; Outdoors; Military/Soldiers; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Facial Hair; Medals/Insignia
  - A group portrait of six young men in front of mountains., 4 March 1970; ref575; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.2 cm (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Men; Mountains/Hills; Damascus, Syria; Arabic Writing; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Outdoors
  - A portrait of two young men on a patio., 24 October 1970; ref576; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 x 7.4 cm (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Damascus, Syria; Mountains/Hills; Men; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Outdoors
  - A group portrait of two men in suits, including Jareh Krikorian, and a small boy outside next to a car., Circa 1965-1975; ref577; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10 x 6.8 cm (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Men; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Boys; Children; Outdoors; Cars/Trucks; Streets/Roads; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Mountains/Hills; Transportation
  - A group portrait of seven men wearing jackets in the snow., 4 March 1970; ref578; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.3 x 7.5 cm (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Snow; Men; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Damascus, Syria; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A group portrait of a man and a woman with a gun, and two small boys., Circa 1965-1975; ref579; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.3 x 7.2 cm (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Arabic Writing; Syria; Women; Men; Guns; Weapons; Children; Boys; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits
  - A group portrait of three men looking at a fabric sample., Circa 1965-1975; ref580; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.3 cm (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Men; Advertisements; Photographic Prints; Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Shops; Facial Hair
  - A group portrait of nine men eating near a body of water., Circa 1965-1975; ref581; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.5 cm (Box 4, Folder 4)
    Men; Water; Bathing Suits/Swimsuits; Cigarettes; Radios; Hats; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Facial Hair; Smoking; Food; Drinks/Beverages
  - A group portrait of five men walking on a railroad track., Circa 1955-1975; ref582; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.3 x 7.3 cm (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Men; Railways; Mountains/Hills; Outdoors; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Syria; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - Two women standing outdoors., Circa 1955-1975; ref583; Samir Color Lab, Saudi Arabia; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.8 x 6.3 cm (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Women; Head Covers/Veils; Jewelry; Color Photography; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Saudi Arabia; Outdoors
  - A group portrait of six men sitting on a bench., Circa 1955-1975; ref584; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.3 x 7.3 cm (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Men; Outdoors; Clocks/Watches; Facial Hair; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria; Group Portraits
  - A group portrait of six young women making gestures., Circa 1955-1975; ref585; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.5 x 6 cm (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Women; Girls; Children; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A portrait of a young man in t-shirt standing outside., Circa 1955-1975; ref586; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10 x 7.2 cm (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - A portrait of a woman wearing a dress standing in a garden., Circa 1955-1975; ref587; Dunia, Derhagopian, Rue Fouad, 1er, Damas (Damascus, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 10 x 7 cm (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Women; Jewelry; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Arabic Writing; Syria; Outdoors; Gardens
  - A portrait of a man facing away from the camera outside., 1970; ref588; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10 x 7.2 cm (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Men; Outdoors; Arabic Writing; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria
  - A group portrait of four men in or around a car., Circa 1955-1975; ref589; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.3 cm (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Men; Cars/Trucks; Outdoors; Arabic Writing; Syria; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Transportation
  - A group portrait of four men wearing suits outdoors., Circa 1955-1975; ref590; Photo Najib, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 x 7.4 cm (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Men; Outdoors; Syria; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Streets/Roads
  - A group portrait of several men outdoors, a few are wearing costumes., Circa 1955-1975; ref591; Tirage Photo Dadour, Alep (Aleppo, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 10.3 x 7.3 cm (Box 4, Folder 5)
    Men; Costumes; Outdoors; Photographic Prints; Aleppo, Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Facial Hair
  - A group portrait of a woman leaning on a man, both are wearing jeans., Circa 1955-1975; ref592; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.2 x 7.2 cm (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Men; Women; Arabic Writing; Syria; Streets/Roads; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A group portrait of a man wearing a suit, a woman wearing a blue dress, and a young girl indoors., February 1959; ref593; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 8.8 x 8.8 cm (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Men; Women; Children; Girls; Houses; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Color Photography; Syria; Furnishings; Carpets/Rugs
  - A group portrait of two men and a woman sitting indoors., Circa 1955-1975; ref594; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.3 x 7.3 cm (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Syria; Men; Women; Head Covers/Veils; Fez/Tarboush; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Furnishings; Facial Hair; Hats
  - A dog tied to a pole., Circa 1955-1975; ref595; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.2 cm (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Dogs; Animals; Streets/Roads; Mountains/Hills; Photographic Prints; Syria; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Cars/Trucks; Transportation
  - A portrait of a man standing on top of a rock and wearing a suit., 1971; ref596; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.2 cm (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Arabic Writing; Men; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Outdoors; Signatures
  - A group portrait of three men at a table in front of a body of water (linked ref598)., Circa 1955-1975; ref597; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 x 7.2 cm (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Hats; Bathing Suits/Swimsuits; Water; Men; Facial Hair; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits
  - A group portrait of three men near a body of water, two are leaning on a tent and one is laying down (linked ref597)., Circa 1955-1975; ref598; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 x 7.4 cm (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Men; Beaches; Water; Tents; Radios; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Facial Hair
  - A portrait of a topless man with glasses outdoors., 16 July 1975; ref599; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.4 cm (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Men; Outdoors; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Arabic Writing; Facial Hair
  - A group portrait of several young children indoors., 1970; ref600; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.3 x 7.4 cm (Box 4, Folder 6)
    Children; Boys; Girls; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Syria
  - A group portrait of two men talking at a wedding., Circa 1955-1975; ref601; Photo Cine Azad, Damascus, [Syria]; 1 Photographic Prints; 12 x 8.5 cm (Box 4, Folder 7)
    Weddings; Men; Women; Gatherings; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Damascus, Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits
  - A portrait of a little boy with his hands on his hips., December 1955; ref602; Yazouy (Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 13.7 x 8.8 cm (Box 4, Folder 7)
    Boys; Furnishings; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria; Children; Toys; Christmas
  - A studio portrait of two men., 2 March 1971; ref603; Studio el Seyahe, Damas (Damascus, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 13.5 x 8.5 cm (Box 4, Folder 7)
    Men; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Facial Hair; Facial Hair; Damascus, Syria; Arabic Writing
  - A group portrait of several men playing a sport., Circa 1955-1975; ref604; Studio Antoin, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.2 x 8.3 cm (Box 4, Folder 7)
    Damascus, Syria; Men; Flags; Uniforms; Sports; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits
  - A studio portrait of a little girl with curly hair wearing a necklace., Circa 1955-1975; ref605; Sadek Qassees, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 13 x 8.3 cm (Box 4, Folder 7)
    Damascus, Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Studio Photography; Jewelry; Girls; Children; Arabic Writing
  - A studio portrait of two men in suits., Circa 1955-1975; ref606; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.2 x 8.4 cm (Box 4, Folder 7)
    Syria; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Men; Facial Hair; Arabic Writing
  - A studio portrait of a man wearing a uniform and a cap., 3 February 1974; ref607; Studio Alsabah, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.3 x 9 cm (Box 4, Folder 7)
    Damascus, Syria; Men; Uniforms; Military/Soldiers; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Hats; Facial Hair; Medals/Insignia
  - A studio portrait of a man wearing a uniform and a cap., Circa 1955-1975; ref608; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.4 x 8.5 cm (Box 4, Folder 7)
    Syria; Arabic Writing; Men; Photographic Prints; Studio Photography; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Military/Soldiers; Uniforms; Hats; Medals/Insignia
  - A portrait of a young boy wearing a swimsuit in the water., Circa 1955-1975; ref609; Photo Kermanik, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.9 x 9 cm (Box 4, Folder 7)
    Boys; Children; Bathing Suits/Swimsuits; Beaches; Water; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Syria
  - A group portrait of a man lifting up another man by his belt., Circa 1955-1975; ref610; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 14 x 8.8 cm (Box 4, Folder 7)
    Men; Outdoors; Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits
  - A studio portrait of a baby on a rocking horse., Circa 1955-1975; ref611; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.6 x 8.7 cm (Box 4, Folder 7)
    Toys; Children; Girls; Studio Photography; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits; Syria
  - A postcard of Fouad I University (now Cairo University), Egypt., 1952; ref612; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 14 x 9 cm (Box 4, Folder 8)
    Postcards; English Writing; Egypt; Universities; Buildings; Architecture; Arabic Writing
  - A postcard of Beyrouth Avenue, Damascus., Circa 1950-1960; ref613; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 14.2 x 9.2 cm (Box 4, Folder 8)
    Damascus, Syria; Mountains/Hills; Streets/Roads; Cars/Trucks; Postcards; Rivers; Mosques; Buildings; Transportation
  - A postcard of Damascus University (Caserne Hamidieh)., Circa 1950-1960; ref614; Unknown; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.9 x 9 cm (Box 4, Folder 8)
    Universities; Damascus, Syria; Postcards; Buildings; Architecture; Military/Soldiers
  - Photo J. Ghazarian studio envelope., Circa 1950-1970; ref615; Photo J. Gazarian, Bab Touma, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 13.4 x 9.5 cm (Box 4, Folder 9)
    Damascus, Syria; Arabic Writing; Signatures; Advertisements; Women; Art; Bathing Suits/Swimsuits; Printed Materials
  - A group portrait of two women, three girls, and two boys indoors., Circa 1950-1970; ref616; Photo J. Gazarian, Bab Touma, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.5 cm (Box 4, Folder 9)
    Women; Boys; Girls; Children; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Damascus, Syria
  - A portrait of a woman holding a dog (linked ref 616)., Circa 1950-1970; ref617; Photo J. Gazarian, Bab Touma, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.3 cm (Box 4, Folder 9)
    Dogs; Animals; Women; Outdoors; Damascus, Syria; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A group portrait of three women, three girls, and two boys indoors (linked ref 616)., Circa 1950-1970; ref618; Photo J. Gazarian, Bab Touma, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.3 cm (Box 4, Folder 9)
    Women; Children; Boys; Girls; Damascus, Syria; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A portrait of a woman holding a dog (linked ref 617)., Circa 1950-1970; ref619; Photo J. Gazarian, Bab Touma, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.3 cm (Box 4, Folder 9)
    Women; Dogs; Animals; Outdoors; Damascus, Syria; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A portrait of a woman with a dog (linked ref 619)., Circa 1950-1970; ref620; Photo J. Gazarian, Bab Touma, Damascus, Syria; 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 7.3 cm (Box 4, Folder 9)
    Women; Dogs; Outdoors; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Animals; Damascus, Syria
  - A portrait of a man in a suit outdoors., Circa 1955-1975; ref621; Studio Hovnan, Damas (Damascus, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 6.3 x 5.3 cm (Box 4, Folder 10)
    Men; Mountains/Hills; Outdoors; Damascus, Syria; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A portrait of a man standing outdoors., Circa 1955-1975; ref622; Studio Hovnan, Damas (Damascus, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 6.4 x 6.4 cm (Box 4, Folder 10)
    Men; Facial Hair; Mountains/Hills; Outdoors; Damascus, Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits
  - A group portrait of several women and one man sitting outdoors., Circa 1955-1975; ref623; Studio Hovnan, Damas (Damascus, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 6.5 x 6.1 cm (Box 4, Folder 10)
    Men; Women; Damascus, Syria; Outdoors; Mountains/Hills; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A portrait of a man overlooking a balcony., Circa 1955-1975; ref624; Studio Hovnan, Damas (Damascus, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 6.5 x 9.5 cm (Box 4, Folder 10)
    Men; Damascus, Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Individual Portraits
  - A studio envelope from Studio Hovnan., Circa 1955-1975; ref625; Studio Hovnan, Damas (Damascus, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 13 x 9 cm (Box 4, Folder 10)
    Damascus, Syria; Arabic Writing; Boys; Individual Portraits; Children; Dogs; Animals; Cameras; Printed Materials; Signatures
  - A studio envelope from Studio Omayad, Damascus., Circa 1955-1975; ref626; Studio Omayad, Rue Fardosse, Damas (Damascus, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 11.8 x 8.1 cm (Box 4, Folder 11)
    Damascus, Syria; Arabic Writing; Studio Photography; Printed Materials
  - A group portrait of a man in a suit and three women outdoors., Circa 1955-1975; ref627; Studio Omayad, Rue Fardosse, Damas (Damascus, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 5.9 x 8.6 cm (Box 4, Folder 11)
    Damascus, Syria; Men; Women; Outdoors; Eye Glasses/Sunglasses; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A group portrait of dressed up men and women in front of a statue of a woman., Circa 1955-1975; ref628; Studio Omayad, Rue Fardosse, Damas (Damascus, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 8.9 x 6.3 cm (Box 4, Folder 11)
    Damascus, Syria; Men; Women; Statues/Sculptures; Children; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits
  - A portrait of a woman sitting on a rock outdoors., Circa 1955-1975; ref629; Studio Omayad, Rue Fardosse, Damas (Damascus, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 8.5 x 6.1 cm (Box 4, Folder 11)
    Photographic Prints; Outdoors; Women; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Damascus, Syria
  - A group portrait of three women indoors., Circa 1955-1975; ref630; Studio Omayad, Rue Fardosse, Damas (Damascus, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 8.6 x 6.1 cm (Box 4, Folder 11)
    Damascus, Syria; Women; Furnishings; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints
  - A group portrait of a woman and a man at a table., Circa 1955-1975; ref631; Studio Omayad, Rue Fardosse, Damas (Damascus, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 10.2 x 7.2 cm (Box 4, Folder 11)
    Damascus, Syria; Men; Women; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Drinks/Beverages
  - A group portrait of smiling man with his arm around a woman (linked ref 631)., Circa 1955-1975; ref632; Studio Omayad, Rue Fardosse, Damas (Damascus, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 10.1 x 6.9 cm (Box 4, Folder 11)
    Men; Women; Damascus, Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Group Portraits; Furnishings
  - A portrait of a woman posing indoors (linked ref632)., Circa 1955-1975; ref633; Studio Omayad, Rue Fardosse, Damas (Damascus, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 10.1 x 7.1 cm (Box 4, Folder 11)
    Women; Jewelry; Damascus, Syria; Photographic Prints; Individual Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Furnishings; Radios
  - An airport strip., Circa 1955-1975; ref634; Studio Omayad, Rue Fardosse, Damas (Damascus, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 x 7.4 cm (Box 4, Folder 11)
    Airplanes; Airports; Men; Damascus, Syria; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Transportation
  - A group portrait of several people near a cliff., 1936; ref635; Dunia, Derhagopian, Rue Fouad, 1er, Damas (Damascus, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 8.6 x 5.7 cm (Box 4, Folder 12)
    Damascus, Syria; Men; Mountains/Hills; Gelatin Silver Prints; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Arabic Writing
  - A group portrait of nine men standing on a rock., Circa 1925-1945; ref636; Dunia, Derhagopian, Rue Fouad, 1er, Damas (Damascus, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 8.7 x 5.8 cm (Box 4, Folder 12)
    Men; Outdoors; Mountains/Hills; Group Portraits; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Damascus, Syria
  - A group portrait of five men on a beach., Circa 1925-1945; ref637; Dunia, Derhagopian, Rue Fouad, 1er, Damas (Damascus, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 11.1 x 6.8 cm (Box 4, Folder 12)
    Men; Beaches; Water; Umbrellas/Parasols; Damascus, Syria; Photographic Prints; Group Portraits; Gelatin Silver Prints; Bathing Suits/Swimsuits; Coast; Facial Hair
  - A group portrait of seven women and two men in the woods., Circa 1925-1945; ref638; Dunia, Derhagopian, Rue Fouad, 1er, Damas (Damascus, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 10.4 x 6.2 cm (Box 4, Folder 12)
    Women; Men; Forest/Woodlands; Outdoors; Photographic Prints; Gelatin Silver Prints; Damascus, Syria; Group Portraits
  - A group portrait of several people in the woods (linked ref 638)., Circa 1925-1945; ref639; Dunia, Derhagopian, Rue Fouad, 1er, Damas (Damascus, Syria); 1 Photographic Prints; 10.5 x 6.3 cm (Box 4, Folder 12)